{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "what will be consider as stand-alone applications?",
            "answers": [
                "An app that executes on a remote computer",
                "An app that includes software control systems",
                "An app that doesn't need a network",
                "An app that stands alone in the registry"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Scrum?",
            "answers": [
                "Framework, it manages work with emphasis on SD",
                "A relatively linear design approach",
                "The process of dividing project management",
                "Description of a software system to be developed"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct order of a waterfall?",
            "answers": [
                "Require ,design, implement ,verify ,maintain",
                "Maintain, design, require, implement, verify",
                "Verify, require, design, maintain, implement",
                "Require, verify, design, implement, maintain"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What of the following is an example of a functional requirements?",
            "answers": [
                "low cost ,reduced time ,no maintenance",
                "risk of data, capacity ceiling,cost",
                "more control, security and performance",
                "lack of control and investment ,slow speed"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "Scenarios should include:",
            "answers": [
                "information about other concurrent activities",
                "participants' system usage hours",
                "design review",
                "participants' professional qualifications"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What of the following is an example of a functional requirement?",
            "answers": [
                "scalability",
                "Reliability",
                "security",
                "external inerfaces"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "Review team is:",
            "answers": [
                "Senior project members",
                "Senior professionals",
                "Customer representatives",
                "All the Answers Are Correct"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "MEDIUM",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is TDD?",
            "answers": [
                "Software development process",
                "Three dimensional diagram",
                "A software system to be developed",
                "Agile framework for managing knowledge work"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "HARD",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is WIMP?",
            "answers": [
                "an agile method",
                "an sdp protocol",
                "A gui requirement",
                "windows, icons, menus, pointers"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "HARD",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the main benifit of unit testing?",
            "answers": [
                "Easy Documentation",
                "All Of These",
                "Facilitates change",
                "Simplifies integration"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "EASY",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many percents of the total cost of product accure during maintenance phase?",
            "answers": [
                "90%",
                "15%",
                "67%",
                "13.5%"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "HARD",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "An example of adaptive maintenance feature is:",
            "answers": [
                "Client requests to improve product UI",
                "response to change in operation environment",
                "correct residual faults",
                "none of the above"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "HARD",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is JSON?",
            "answers": [
                "Evil character in movies",
                "JavaScript Object Notation",
                "An array of Json files",
                "Journalistic Stream Of News"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "EASY",
            "team": "LIONS"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the purpose of Reviews?",
            "answers": [
                "Good Reviews => Increased Revenue",
                "To check how much your team is talented",
                "A filter, removes defects percentage",
                "Staying on budget"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "HARD",
            "team": "LIONS"
        }
    ]
}